Guide to the Lesly Lempert Collection, 1987-1994.
Lempert, Lesly Collection
- Series I. Periodicals
  - (Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Preping the Way for Palestine: Health and Human Rights, June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    Producer: Ruchama Marton
  - (Ninth United Nations North American NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): [Miscellaneous Symposium and Participant Information], June 24-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - The Origins and Evolution of the Palestine Problem: 1917-1988, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 392)
    Producer: United Nations, Committee on the Exercise of the Inalienable Rights of the Palestinian People
  - The Question of the Observance of the Fourth Geneva Convention of 1949 in Gaza and the West Bank including Jerusalem Occupied by Israel in June 1967, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - United Nations International NGO Meeting on the Question of Palestine [papers], September 7-9, 1987--August 29-31, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - (Fourth United Nations International NGO Meeting on the Question of Palestine), September 7-9, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - (List of Participants: Fourth United Nations International NGO Meeting on the Question of Palestine), January 18, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - (Seventh United Nations International NGO Meeting on the Question of Palestine), August 29-31, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - United Nations North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine, June 27-29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - (United Nations North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Introduction, June 27-29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - (United Nations North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Declaration and Plan of Action Adopted by the North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine, June 27-29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - (United Nations North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Resolutions Adopted by the North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine, June 27-29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - (United Nations North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): 1900-1991 North American Co-ordinating Committee for NGOs on the Question of Palestine, June 27-29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - (United Nations North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): Message to the Symposium from H.E. Mr. Yasser Arafat, Chairman of the Executive Committee of the Palestine Liberation Organization, June 27-29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - (United Nations North American Regional NGO Symposium on the Question of Palestine): List of Participants and Observers, June 27-29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - Universal Declaration of Human Rights: G.A. Res. 217A (III), U.N. Doc. A/810, at 71 (1948) (2), 1948; photocopy, p. 17-8 (Box 7, Folder 396)
  - Water Resources of the Occupied Palestinian Territory, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 397)
  - Newsletter, Fall 1990 (Box 7, Folder 398)
    Producer: US/Israel Women-to-Women
    Volume/Number: 2.1
  - Creeping Transfer' Taking Place in the West Bank, October 2, 1989; draft, typescript, 5 leaves (Box 7, Folder 399)
    Producer: Washington Report on Middle East Affairs
  - Irrigation Minister on Water, al-Wahdah Dam (from various sources), February 12, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 400)
    Producer: Al-Watan al-'Arabi
  - Administrative Detention in the occupied West Bank, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 401)
    Producer: West Bank affiliate of the Internation Commission of Jurists, Emma Playfair
  - Newsletter, June/July/August 1995 (Box 7, Folder 402)
    Producer: Women's Organization for Political Prisoners (WOFPP)
  - National Newsletter, Winter 1992-93 (Box 7, Folder 403)
    Producer: Women in Black
  - Health Conditions of the Arab Population in the Occupied Arab Territories, Including Palestine, May 5, 1991; two fragmented copies, transmissions (Box 7, Folder 404)
    Producer: World Health Organization
  - [Articles pertaining to Beita], April 10, 1988--July 14, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: (various publications)
  - (Article): Moving Towards the Bring, April 10, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Settler Girl was Killed by Bulled from Guard's Rifle, April 10, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Joel Greenberg, Kenneth Kaplan, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): 'Nobody Should Take Children into a Battlefield': Local Arabs Indignant about 'Needless and Avoidable' Deaths at Beita, April 11, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Troops Uproot Trees at Beita, April 11, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Joel Greenberg, Bradley Burston, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Elon Moreh Teenagers Give Their Version: 'Aldubi was Not Firing When Tirza Porat Fell', April 11, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Joel Greenberg, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Herzog: 'Don't Drag IDF Into Politics': Likud Ministers Rap IDF of Beita Probe, April 11, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Menachem Shalev, Devorah Getzler, Michal Yudelman
  - (Article): High Court Petiitioned on Demolitions, April 11, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Army Stands by Its Version, April 11, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Beita Escorts Both Have Stormy Pasts, April 11, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Gershom Gorenberg, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Storming the Ramparts, April 11, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Not Fit for the Job, April 12, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Shomron Warns Knesset Committee: 'Don't Expect Surprises in Beita Probe', April 13, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Government to Censor Arab Press Releases, April 14, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Elaine Ruth Fletcher, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): IDF Denies Use of Highly Toxic Tear Gas, April 14, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Libai Slams Sharir as Unfit to Hold Office, April 14, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Strict New Measures Considered to Curb Gazans, April 14, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Two Gaza Rioters Shot, April 14, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Many Guilty Parties in the Beita Affair, April 15, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Shomron Says Staying in Territories Requires Doing Extra Reserve Duty, April 15, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): A Tragedy of Errors, April 15, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): When Tragedy is Exploited Politically, April 15, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Arye Naor
  - (Article): Toward the Extreme, April 24, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Anthony Lewis, New York Times
  - (Article): Mitzna: Tirza Porat was killed by Romam Aldubi, April 28, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Gratitude to Women of Beita, April 28, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Ruth Duek, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Shomron's Description Angers W. Bank Settlers, May 12, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Joshua Brilliant, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Back to Beita, May 12, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: [Jerusalem Post?]
  - (Article): Deliberate Policy, May 13, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Nachum Mandel, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): 'Encouraging' Responses to Operation ID in Gaza Strip, May 13, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Bradley Burston, Joel Greenberg, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Shomron: Settlers Source of Tension in W. Bank, May 13, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - June 6, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Israeli Group Works for Arab Village, July 24, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Glenn Frankel, Washington Post
  - (Article): Where the Hot Rage of April Is Now Cold Fury, August 23, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Joel Brinkley, New York Times
  - (Article): Beita Villagers Plead Not Guilty, September 9, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): All Quiet as 2,000 Take Part in 41 Hikes Through Territories, February 7, 1989; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - February 7, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - February 7, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - February 7, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Settler Guard in Beita Incident Recognized as 'Disabled Soldier', June 30, 1989; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Alibi Accepted After 14 Months in Jail, July 7, 1989; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
    Producer: Michal Sela
  - July 7, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Beita Aftermath: Villagers Sentenced to 4 Years in Jail, July 14, 1989; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): East Jerusalem Merchants to Court on Closure Violations, [?]; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - (Article): Let the Healing Begin On the West Bank, [?]; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - [Articles pertaining to Civil Rights of Palestinians], October 17, 1983--June 26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 406)
  - (Article): Jewish Group Claims Israel Denies Individual Liberties, October 17, 1983; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: B.J. Palermo, Daily News
  - (Article): Rally Focuses on Israel's Civil Rights: Personal Liberties Trampled, Westside Fund-Raiser Is Told, October 17, 1983; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: Mary Curtius, Los Angeles Times
  - (Article): Letters to The Times: 'Rally Focuses on Israeli Rights', October 26, 1983; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: (multiple authors), Los Angeles Times
  - (Article): Letters to The Times: Israeli Rally, November 2, 1983; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: George Slaff, Los Angeles Times
  - (Article): Letters to the Times: Civil Rights in Israel, November 6, 1983; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: Stanley K. Sheinbaum, Los Angeles Times
  - (Article): Not All Jews Embrace Israeli Belligerence, March 20, 1992; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: Colman McCarthy, Seattle Times
  - (Article): Rabin's Win Not Enough to Stop Pain of Palestinian Kids, June 26, 1992; photocopy, on back of above article (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: Barbara Reynolds, USA Today
  - (Article): Letters to The Times: 'Humanity Will Not Forgive This', [?]; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 406)
  - (Article): An Alternative to Conflict: A Peace Activist's Opinion, [?]; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: Joel Nathan, The Nation
  - (Article): Beyond the Green Line: A Jewish Settler's Opinion, [?] (Box 7, Folder 406)
    Producer: Hank Nussbacher, The Nation
  - (Article): Extracts from the Report on the Landau Commission's Inquiry into the Workings of the Shin Bet: How Does a Democratic Country Deal with Terrorism?, [?] (Box 7, Folder 406)
  - [Articles pertaining to Curfew], January 7, 1991--January 30, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Scattered clashes as Gaza Strip on strike, January 7, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Rural residents get masks, January 8, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Palestinians stock up on food, medicines in event of attack, January 13, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Palestinians in Occupied Territories Face War Unprepared, January 14, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    Producer: Sabra Chartrand, New York Times
  - (Article): Curfews to prevent deadline day disorders, January 17, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Curfews in areas bring building to standstill, January 25, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    Producer: Bill Hutman, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Palestinians fear month-long curfew, January 25, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Rural areas may get masks, January 26, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Area's curfew stifling building: Sharon, January 28, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    Producer: Herb Keinon, [?]
  - (Article): NGOs say situation is critical; lack of food and medicine, January 28, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    Producer: Ghada Turjman, Lesley Abukhater, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): High Court turns down request for gas mask distribution in Ketzoit, January 29, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Palestinians are short of money, food, January 29, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - (Article): Defense kits and discrimination, January 30, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    Producer: Asher Felix Landau, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Curfews discussed, January 30, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    Producer: Alisa Odenheimer
  - [Articles pertaining to Deportation], February 6, 1987--Feburary 1, 1990; photocopies (Box 7, Folder 408)
  - (Article): [Article about Family Reunification and Deportation], February 6, 1987; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 408)
    Producer: Jerusalem Post Magazine
  - (Article): The Invisible Transfer, September 15, 1989; typescript (Box 7, Folder 408)
    Producer: Goga Kogan, Hotam
  - (Article): The Transfer Has Begun and Proceeds without a Hitch, September 20, 1989; typescript (Box 7, Folder 408)
    Producer: Gabi Nitan, Hadashot
  - (Article): What's New with Rabin's Transfer, October 18, 1989; typescript (Box 7, Folder 408)
  - (Article): Special Report: "Creeping Transfer"-Israel's Newest Weapon Against the Intifada, November, 1989; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 408)
    Producer: Jerry Levin, Washington Report on Middle East Affairs
  - (Article): Expulsion of women-another facet of a grand scheme, January 23, 1990; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 408)
    Producer: Sana Atiyeh, Jordan Times
  - (Article): 'Non-Resident' Palestinians Forced Out: Rights Groups Assail Deportations as Being Politically Motivated, January 30, 1990; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 408)
    Producer: Jackson Diehl, Washington Post
  - (Article): Israel Temorarily Halts West Bank Deportations: Move Follows State Department Criticism, February 1, 1990; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 408)
    Producer: Sami Aboudi, Washington Post
  - West Bank's Hidden Housing Boom: Government Smoke Screen Obscures Vast Jewish Settlement Program, January 29, 1992; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 408 A)
  - No Letup in Construction at West Bank Settlement: 'Political' or 'Security' Role is at Issue, July 23, 1992; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 408 A)
    Producer: David Hoffman, Washington Post
  - [Articles pertaining to Israel and Jordan], July 4, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 409)
  - (Article): First, Israel and Jordan Can Reach Some Accords, July 4, 1990; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 409)
    Producer: Gideon Rafael, International Herald Tribune
  - (Article): First, Israel and Jordan Can Reach Some Accords, July 4, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 409)
  - (Article): Jordan is Palestine, [?] (Box 7, Folder 409)
    Producer: David Singer, Jerusalem Post
  - [Articles pertaining to Israeli Arabs], April 13, 1988--December 29, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): The Green Line-Growing Fainter for Israeli Arabs, April 13, 1988; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Debt-ridden Arab councils to begin indefinite strike today over 'broken promises', February 5, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Equality for all citizens, February 16, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Fed-up heads of Arab councils take their beef to the Interior Ministry, February 16, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Israeli Arabs decry Jewish 'indifference' to money crisis, February 20, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Ben Lynfield, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Israeli Arab warns of violence, February 21, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: David Rudge, Ben Lynfield, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Arab councils end strike after accord with banks, February 28, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): A zigzag attitude to Arab equality, March 9, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Angry at U.S. Rebuff, Jerusalem Tries to Show How Well It Treats Arabs, March 10, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Disappointed Arab council heads decide to renew municipal strike, March 25, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Arab councils seek allies on debt issue, March 28, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Jewish councillors join Arab protests, April 2, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Arab MKs decide on campaign to combat 'racist' comments, April 15, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Self-help for Galilee Arabs, April 20, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Book fair bans Yesh Gvul stand, May 4, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Dan Izenberg, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Israeli Arabs, Feeling Adrift, Talk of Rising Identity Crisis, May 22, 1990; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Alan Cowell, New York Times
  - (Article): The vast majority of Israel Arabs did not riot: Intifada inside the Green Line?, May 24, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Yosef Goell, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Not a minor problem, June 1, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Marcia Kretzmer, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Arab towns protest education flaws, handling of riots, June 7, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: David Rudge, Lea Levavi, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): The Palestinization of Israeli Arabs, June 11, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Elie Rekhess, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Mixed reactions from Israeli Arabs, June 15, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Rishon and Israeli Arabs, June 20, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Where there's muck, there are jobs too, June 22, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Which comes first, politics or business? It’s a dilemma for many Israeli Arabs, June 22, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Israeli Arabs welcome Olmert's effort to raise standard of living, June 26, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - (Article): Islamic college for Israel's Arabs, July 5, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Marda Dunsky, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Israel's Arab Social Gap, March 12, 1992; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Kenneth Bandler, Christian Science Monitor
  - (Article): Guests Can Be Shown the Door, December 13, 1992; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: David Grossman, New York Times Magazine
  - (Article): The Arab Revolutionaries, December 29, 1994; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 410)
    Producer: Leslie Susser, Jerusalem Report
  - Shabbat sensitivity is a two-way street (draft, typescript), July 18, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 410 A)
  - Doing right by the loyal Druse (draft, typescript), May 7, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 410A)
  - [Articles pertaining to Justice Minister Dan Meridor], June 7, 1989--January 7, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 411)
  - (Article): Meridor bypassed legal experts on Jewish terror case, June 7, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 411)
    Producer: Oz Frankel, (multiple authors), Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Meridor: collective punishment justified to suppress intifada, September 26, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 411)
    Producer: David Makovsky, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Meridor defends Israel's rights record in areas, November 22, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 411)
  - (Article): Begin defends Meridor from far-right onslaught, January 7, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 411)
    Producer: Sarah Honig, Michal Yudelman, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Meridor scores those who see legal process as stumbling block, July [?] (Box 7, Folder 411)
    Producer: Dvorah Getzler
  - [Articles pertaining to Meir Kahane and Kahanism], November 9, 1985--January 5, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 412)
  - (Article): Kahaneism, November 9, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 412)
    Producer: Amos Kenan, The Nation
  - (Article): Kahane's Rise Troubles Jews in U.S., November 29, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 412)
    Producer: Richard J. Meislin, New York Times
  - (Article): For Peace and an Independent Palestine, January 5, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 412)
    Producer: Rachelle Marshall, New York Times
  - [Articles pertaining to Temple Mount], October 14, 1990--June 21, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
  - (Article): Temple Mount: Palestinian, Israeli Versions Don't Tell Real Story, October 14, 1990; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
    Producer: Washington Post
  - (Article): The Battle at Temple Mount: Neither Palestinian Nor Israeli Version Tells Full Story, October 14, 1990; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
  - (Article): Editorial: Temple Mount: The Real Story, November 12, 1990; photocopy (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
    Producer: Mortimer B. Zuckerman, U.S. News & World Report
  - (Article): New Evidence: Two Startling Videotapes Support Arab Changes, [November 13, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
    Producer: Michael Emery, [The Village Voice]
  - (Article): Judgement on Temple Mount: The battle moves to the High Court of Jusice, [June 21, 1991] (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
    Producer: Abraham Rabinovich, [Jerusalem Post]
  - (Article): Reporters, Lies, and Videotapes, [?] (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
    Producer: Mel Rosen, The Village Voice
  - (Article): The Terrible Toll: Medics Give Eyewitness Accouts of the Shootings-Including Their Own, [?] (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
    Producer: Michael Emery, Ibrahim Dawud, The Village Voice
  - (Article): Meanwhile in Brooklyn…The Palestinians Watch and Wait, [?] (Box 7, Folder 412 A)
    Producer: Alisa Solomon, The Village Voice
  - [Articles pertaining to Undercover Units], April 12, 1992--March 10, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 B)
  - (Article): Killings of Palestinian Suspects Raise Questions About Israeli Army Agents, April 12, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 412 B)
  - (Article): Israeli Couple Disputes Army Account of Shooting, April 22, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 412 B)
  - (Article): IDF undercover soldiers proud of controversial job, January 8, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 B)
  - (Article): The acceptable level of violence, March 10, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 B)
  - [Articles pertaining to Legal Rulings of the High Court], June 7, 1993--July 12, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 C)
  - (Article): Ordinary courts, not High Court, should deal with Jewish agency, June 7, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 C)
  - (Article): Barring entry to the Mount, June 14, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 C)
  - (Article): Court is peacemaker in family feud over epitaph, June 28, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 C)
  - (Article): Religion plea no reason to halt extradition, July 12, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 C)
  - The Jerusalem Post Law Reports, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 412 c)
  - [Articles pertaining to Basic Laws], [April 13, 1992--June 19, 1992] (Box 7, Folder 412 D)
    Producer: (various authors), [Jerusalem Post]
  - (Article): Elections: The race is on, [April 13, 1992] (Box 7, Folder 412 D)
    Producer: Dan Izenberg, [Jerusalem Post]
  - (Article): We don't need more reform, [April 15, 1992] (Box 7, Folder 412 D)
    Producer: Uriel Lynn, [Jerusalem Post]
  - (Article): The Supreme Court's weighty task, [May 24, 1992] (Box 7, Folder 412 D)
    Producer: Aharon Barak, [Jerusalem Post]
  - (Article): A revolution whose name has come, [June 19, 1992] (Box 7, Folder 412 D)
    Producer: Allan E. Shapiro, [Jerusalem Post]
  - [Articles pertaining to Settlement], February 28, 1990--August 13, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - (Article): The Battleground from the Jordan to the Sea, February 28, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 413)
    Producer: Marc D. Charney, New York Times
  - (Article): West Bank's 'Garden Views and Special Loans' Are Luring Jewish Settlers, March 4, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - (Article): Eating up Arab Jerusalem: Teddy Kollek's rights issue, April 30, 1990; photocopy (Box 8, Folder 413)
    Producer: Paul Ajiouny, Al-Fajr
  - (Article): 'Settling' in East Jerusalem, September 3, 1990; photocopy (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - (Article): Israel's Latest Push to Attract Investors, December 2, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 413)
    Producer: Sara Krulwich, New York Times
  - (Article): Immigration and the new budget, December 25, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 413)
    Producer: Alisa Odenheimer, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Economy, organization and settlement, January 11, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 413)
    Producer: Ra'anan Weitz, Jerusalem Post